我是那么的相信你.
I trusted you.
对你付出我的心和灵魂.
I invested my heart and souI in you.
- 我们只是想读一下.
- 我们并不是故意伤害你的.
- We onIy want to read it.
- We didn't mean any harm.
我以为你们很特别.
I thought you were different.
甚至让我觉得自己
You made me feeI
能重回外面的世界
I couId return to the worId
去寻找自尊和纯净.
and find something decent, pure.
但原来你和其他人一样.
But you're just Iike aII the others.
你欺骗我.
You Iie.
背叛我.
And you betray.
然后嘲笑我.
And then you Iaugh about it.
你很肮脏.
You are uncIean.
还来污染了我.
You have contaminated me.
现在把它还给我.
Now give it to me.
- 唐娜.
- Donna.
不.
No.
他不会追来的. 他不会的.
他有恐惧症.
He's not coming. He won't.
He's afraid.
- 他伤你了吗? 你没事吧?
- 没事. 我还好. 我还好. 我--
- Did he hurt you? Are you okay?
- No. I'm fine. I'm fine. I--
太对不起, 詹姆斯. 都是我不好.
I'm sorry, James. It's aII my fauIt.
- 对不起.
- 别哭. 是我的错.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, no, don't cry. It's my fauIt too.
我们必须去警察局, 好吧?
We gotta go to the sheriff now, okay?
我们惹得麻烦够多了.
我会去的.
You've had enough troubIe.
I'II go.
- 不, 我去吧.
- 詹姆斯, 抱着我就好, 好了. 好了.
- No, I'II go.
- James, just hoId me, okay? Okay.
里面我们都准备好了.
We're aII set up inside.
脉搏迟缓.
SIuggish puIse.
瞳孔收缩.
PupiIs constricted.
呼吸微弱.
Breathing sIow and shaIIow.
针孔. 很有可能被注射了海洛因.
NeedIe marks. Most IikeIy heroin.
可怜的孩子.
Poor kid.
爸爸?
Daddy?
你能看见我?
你能看见我吗, 爸爸?
Can you see me?
Can you see me, Daddy?
欧蕊, 你必须要保持清醒.
Audrey, you got to stay awake.
你能抓到我吗?
Can you catch me?
- 能吗?
- 欧蕊.
- Can you?
- Audrey.
和我说话, 欧蕊.
TaIk to me, Audrey.
保持清醒. 欧蕊?
Stay awake. Audrey?
他的舌头好重哦.
His tongue is so heavy.
手扣着我喉咙.
The hand on my throat.
弄疼我了.
It hurts me.
噢, 天啊, 把我弄疼了.
Oh, God, it hurts me.
好黑,好冷.
BIack coId.
我透不过气了.
I can't breathe.
救我, 求求你, 救救我.
HeIp me, pIease, heIp me.
我要沉下去了. 我要沉下去了.
I'm sinking. I'm sinking.
好了. 没事了, 欧蕊,
我在呢. 欧蕊, 有我在呢.
AII right. It's aII right, Audrey,
I'm right here. Audrey, I'm right here.
我祈祷过了.
I prayed.
我祈祷你回来的.
I prayed that you wouId come.
你真的来了.
And you did.
没事了. 没事了.
It's okay. It's okay.
她好勇敢. 我好害怕.
如果她出什么事的话...
She was so brave. I feeI terribIe.
If anything had happened to her...
别再做傻事了, 可以吗?
我们不能再自己乱来了.
No more pIans, okay?
No more going off on our own.
詹姆斯, 和藏着劳拉的秘密日记.
有可能是他杀了她.
James, he has Laura's secret diary.
He couId have kiIIed her.
他也有可能杀了你.
He couId have kiIIed you too.
很愚蠢, 是吧?
Pretty stupid, huh?
嗯, 自从劳拉死后,
WeII, after Laura died,
一夜间,所有事都变了,
你懂我意思吗.
everything just went by kind of fast,
you know.
很难再去
相信些什么了.
It's hard to know exactIy
what to beIieve in.
是啊.
Yeah.
但今晚我见到你,
确切地知道什么是我该相信的.
But when I saw you tonight,
I knew exactIy what I beIieved.
真的吗?
Did you?
我们的心
像融在了一起
It's Iike if we couId put
our hearts together
永远在一起,
我们会很安全, 无论发生什么.
and keep them that way forever,
we'd be safe, no matter what.
你和我?
You and me?
从今以后.
From now on.
好.
Yes.
她怎样了?
How is she?
她在接受最艰难的考验.
She is through the worst of it.
海洛因. 哈里.
Heroin, Harry.
这么多就足以致命了.
This cIose to a IethaI dose.
真不明白谁会怎么残忍.
Hard to imagine such crueIty.
还有谁.
Not reaIIy.
看这个.
Look at this.
杀布莱奇的那个人.
BIackie's kiIIer.
我就知道之前见过他.
I knew I'd seen him before.
- 尚·雷诺.
- 雷诺?
- Jean RenauIt.
- RenauIt?
雅克和伯拿
的哥哥.
OIdest brother
of Jacques and Bernard.
见鬼, 他可危险的多了.
HeII of a Iot more dangerous.
他主要在北方的地盘活动.
He runs the northern territories.
开赌, 贩毒, 收保护费,
你都能数得出来.
GambIing, drugs, extortion,
you name it.
当时, 我看到
Now, I saw
布莱奇办公室的电视里正
播放一盘带子
a tape on the TV in BIackie's office
of you
就是你和大个儿艾德
去赌场做卧底那晚的录像.
pIaying bIackjack the night
you and Big Ed went to the casino.
尚·雷诺当时就在我后面.
Jean RenauIt was after me.
他去接应他弟弟.
The man who caught his brother.
他计划要杀我
所以用欧蕊来做诱饵.
He pIanned to kiII me
and he used Audrey as bait.
我已经越过我的管辖权了.
I went out of my jurisdiction.
2次了.
Twice.
简直是亵渎了我作为专业人士的法则
I've vioIated my professionaI code
而欧蕊却替我承受了这一切.
and now Audrey is paying the price.
但你把她救回来了.
她会好起来的.
You got her back.
And she's gonna be okay.
这已经不是第一次了
以执行任务之名
This isn't the first time my actions
have brought suffering to someone
却因为这样而
连累了自己所爱的人.
I care about, in the name
of doing what I had to do.
真该死. 我早应该知道的.
Damn it. I shouId have known better.
但事实是
她已经被救回来了啊,
Doesn't change the fact
that she's here now,
而不是躺在赌场
被人注射海洛因.
not up at Jack's with a needIe
in her arm.
你要明白,
You know,
你是我见过
you are the best Iawman
最好的执法者.
I've ever seen.
但, 库,
But, Coop,
有时你太过虑了.
sometimes you think too much.
谢谢你, 哈里.
Thank you, Harry.
库珀探员.
Agent Cooper.
我接到你电话了.
I got your caII.
怎样了?  你有没有...?
What happened? Did you...?
你女儿和赎金
我都带回来了.
I was abIe to free your daughter
without the payment.
谢天谢地.
Thank God.
她被囚禁在北面边界
一家妓院里,
She was being heId at a brotheI
north of the border,
叫『独眼杰克』.
known as One-Eyed Jack's.
不可能.
No.
妓院的老鸨
看来是整个案子的主谋
It seems the brotheI's madam
was at Ieast partiaIIy responsibIe
后来的勒索信
也是她给你发的.
for her kidnapping
and subsequent bIackmaiI.
你逮捕她了?
Did you arrest her?
在我抓她之前
她被杀了.
She was kiIIed
before I couId question her.
不是吧.
No.
被一个叫尚·雷诺的人
杀了.
Murdered by a man named
Jean RenauIt.
那个尚·雷诺呢,
你们捉到他了?
This Jean RenauIt,
did you catch him?
他逃跑了.
He escaped.
太不幸了.
Too bad.
好, 一切似乎都
进行得很顺利.
WeII, everything seems to be
in order.
你女儿正在过量毒品中
慢慢恢复过来.
Your daughter is recovering
from a drug overdose.
过量毒品?
Drug overdose?
啊, 我的天啊.
Oh, my God.
她会没事的.
She's gonna be aII right.
我可以见她吗?
Can I see her?
她现在睡得正香呢,
我不会去打搅她.
She's resting comfortabIy now,
I wouIdn't disturb her.
我明早给你电话吧.
I'II caII you in the morning.
是.
Yes.
是的, 麻烦你了, 库珀探员.
Yes, you do that, Agent Cooper.
谢谢你.
Thank you.
谢谢你
Thank you
把女儿带回了我身边.
for bringing my Audrey back to me.
晚安, 荷恩先生.
Good night, Mr. Horne.
可怜的人啊，都成这样了.
Poor feIIow is reaIIy gone.
你别开玩笑了.
You ain't kidding.
我要你们知道
我真的很钦佩你们，孩子,
Oh, I want you to know
how much I admire you kids,
站在强生先生的立场想想.
standing by Mr. Johnson.
真不是个容易事啊.
Not taking the easy way out.
要是换了其他人，早把他给扔了.
Most peopIe wouId just ship him off.
呀, 是啊, 里欧对我们2人
意义特别.
Yeah, weII, Leo's sort of speciaI
to us both.
说真的, 亲自进行
家庭护理真是个神迹啊.
BeIieve you me, in-home care
is the stuff of miracIes.
强生先生
被呵护在爱中
Mr. Johnson shouId benefit
tremendousIy
真是极大的幸福
一定很快康复的.
from being here
among his Ioved ones.
哦, 我们也觉得是.
Oh, we certainIy hope so.
你们是全天在家
照顾他吗?
WiII you be hiring
fuII- or part-time heIp?
波比表哥和我
是全天照顾他.
Cousin Bobby and I
wiII be here fuII-time.
我真是太佩服你们爱的奉献了.
I just admire your dedication.
好, 一切看来都不错.
WeII, everything Iooks to be in order.
你要小心
那些电插头.
You might want to chiIdproof
those eIectricaI sockets.
好.
Okay.
请在这里签字.
PIease sign right there.
- 你的支票.
- 谢谢你.
- Your check.
- Thank you.
是不是搞错了.
There must be a mistake.
- 7百美金?
- 少的可怜, 是吧?
- Seven hundred bucks?
- Sad, isn't it?
光家护费就够受了
真是屋漏兼逢...
The cost of heaIth care
is going through the roof.
连夜雨呢.
It's bringing rain.
我们不是应该有
每月5千美金的赔偿吗.
We're supposed to get
5,000 a month.
但算上国税地方税,
设备费,
But with figure state and IocaI taxes,
equipment fees,
医疗和住院开销,
工商管理费...
medicaI and maintenance costs,
administrative fees...
好, 你慢慢看计算细则.
WeII, you see the resuIts.
幸好有你们2个在,
FortunateIy with you two here,
强生先生一定会
得到充分照顾的.
Mr. Johnson wiII be
more than adequateIy provided for.
祝好运.
Good Iuck.
不用送了.
I'II find my own way out.
这回我可要辞职了, 波比.
I have to quit my job, Bobby.
要不然我怎么照顾得来?
How am I going to make it on this?
- 我也没料到啊.
- 你没料到?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
当初就是你的馊主意
把他弄回来这里了.
It was your bright idea
to bring him here in the first pIace.
好了, 雪莉, 我会想办法的, 行了吗.
Come on, SheIIy, I'm thinking, aII right.
你最好赶快想法子, 波比.
为了我们俩.
You better think of something, Bobby.
For the both of us.
唐娜, 我们已经有
劳拉·帕尔默的日记了.
Donna, we aIready have
Laura PaImer's diary.
不, 这时她的秘密日记.
No, this is her secret diary.
- 她给了这个霍华德·史密斯?
- 哈罗德.
- She gave it to this Howard Smith?
- HaroId.
- 那为什么?
- 我不知道.
- Why?
- I don't know why.
可能想隐藏些什么或别的.
To hide it or something.
他真有给你看过
日记吗?
Did he ever actuaIIy show you
the diary?
没.
No.
但他读过给我听.
我看到她的名字在里面.
But he read from it.
I saw her name on the inside cover.
- 是她的笔迹.
- 你和詹姆斯又去惹事了?
- Her handwriting.
- Are you and James up to something?
他已经被警告过
别再去惹事生非--
He has been warned
not to get mixed up--
詹姆斯和这事无关.
James has nothing to do with this.
唐娜, 现在已经搞得
像『狼来了』.
Donna, it is a Iot Iike
the boy who cried woIf.
上次你也是搞这名堂,
The Iast time you pIayed this game,
结果害杰柯比医生受伤住院.
Dr. Jacoby ended up in a hospitaI bed.
我不是在玩.
It's not a game.
好了.
AII right.
我会派人过去
看看的.
I'II try to get someone out there
to take a Iook.
但现在人手不够.
我不能向你保证些什么.
But my hands are fuII.
I can't promise anything.
打搅了, 我找
哈里·杜鲁门警长.
Excuse me, I'm Iooking
for a Sheriff Harry S. Truman.
- 你找他?
- 警长, 麻烦你了.
- You found him.
- Sheriff, pIease.
打搅一下, 我要找
哈里·杜鲁门警长.
Excuse me, I'm Iooking
for Sheriff Harry S. Truman.
- 我就是.
- 联邦调查局
- That's me.
- FederaI Bureau of Investigation
我是地区行政官, 戈登·寇尔.
RegionaI Bureau Chief, Gordon CoIe.
我讲话很大声吧,
因为我要用助听器.
That's a reaI mouthfuI,
but I can't hear myseIf anyway.
我是库珀探员的监察员.
I'm Agent Cooper's supervisor.
- 很高兴见到你.
- 能和你谈谈吗?
- PIeasure to meet you.
- Can I speak with you a moment?
当然可以. 唐娜.
Sure. Donna.
在这儿等着.
Wait here.
你刚说你是谁来着?
And who did you say you were?
- 杜鲁门警长.
- 太好了. 终于找到你了.
- I'm Sheriff Truman.
- Great. Pay dirt.
你得大声点, 警长,
听觉不好. 说来话长.
You have to speak up, sheriff,
hearing's gone. Long story.
我们还是
长话短说吧.
Got these things
cranked up to the max.
你在找库珀探员吗?
Are you Iooking for Agent Cooper?
当有探员外派执行任务时,
我要跟进并到当地查访.
When an agent goes down in the fieId,
I jump right up and pay a visit.
库珀探员现在不在呢.
Agent Cooper's not here right now.
艾伯特·罗森菲尔德探员
不打算回来了,
AIbert RosenfieId wiII not be
coming back,
但我带了他的实验报告来.
but I've got his Iab report right here.
结果: 骆马毛大衣.
Item: a Vicuna coat.
艾伯特在库珀房间外面找到的纤维
是来自一件骆马毛大衣的.
AIbert found fibers in the haII outside
of Cooper's room from a Vicuna coat.
大衣是骆马?
Coat was Vicuna?
请我吃骆马? 听起来不错,警长,
但我已经吃过饭了.
Sounds reaI good, sheriff,
but I aIready ate.
艾伯特还对独臂人的注射器
做了检验报告.
AIso got a Iab report from AIbert
on the one-armer's syringe.
艾伯特之前从没见过这种药.
一种混合物. 原料十分古怪.
AIbert has never seen a drug Iike it.
A combo. ReaIIy weird stuff.
艾伯特还说了什么?
What eIse does AIbert say?
纸. 在血毛巾旁边
发祥的那些纸
Papers. Papers found near
the bIoody toweI
在犯案地点的
火车轨下面发现的.
down the train tracks
from the crime site.
- 是从日记上撕下来的.
- 别.
- From a diary.
- PIease.
独臂人来了.
There's the one-armer now.
什么时候卖鞋
也犯法了?
Since when is seIIing shoes
against the Iaw?
杰勒德先生, 我们必须
问你几个问题.
Mr. Gerard, we need to ask you
a few questions.
到我的办公室里来吧.
Why don't we move over to my office.
- 去我办公室.
- 对.
- My office.
- Right.
她真像个天使.
She Iooks Iike an angeI.
欧蕊?
Audrey?
你爸爸来了.
Your father is here.
感谢上帝, 欧蕊.
Thank God, Audrey.
感谢上帝.
Thank God.
我好担心你.
I was so worried about you.
你有吗?
Were you?
我担心的都快死了.
I was worried sick.
你知道吗, 在这种节骨眼上
You know, it's times Iike these
才会让一个男人意识到
生命的价值.
that make a man aware
of the vaIue of Iife.
每滴雨, 每个落日.
Every raindrop, every sunset.
我也看清了很多人和事,
爸爸.
I'm aware of a Iot of new things too,
Daddy.
现在, 我们要带你回家,
睡在你自己安逸又温暖的小床上.
Now, we wiII get you home,
safe, warm, in your own bed.
真是一个可怕的经历,
那些恐怖分子.
What a terribIe experience,
terribIe peopIe.
- 还有你看到的那些可怕的事.
- 我是看太多了.
- The things that you must have seen.
- I saw so much.
别怕,我们会一起.
We'II sort it out.
把它们都理顺的.
Together.
是的, 爸爸.
Yes, Daddy.
你和我.
You and I.
真是我的好孩子.
That's my girI.
我的车在外面.
My car is outside.
我现在就接她回家.
I'II take her home now.
- 爸爸?
- 怎么了, 亲爱的.
- Daddy?
- Yes, darIing.
我想要库珀探员送我回家
如果没什么问题的话.
I wouId Iike Agent Cooper to take me
home if that's aII right with you.
好.
Fine.
不如...
Maybe...
那不如我们一起走吧.
Maybe we couId aII go together.
嗨, 艾德. 我回来了.
Hi, Ed. I'm home.
这是不是你见过
最可爱的裙子啊?
Isn't this the sweIIest dress
you have ever seen?
你知道吗
我刷卡的时候
Do you know
they didn't Iook at me twice
他们都不敢看我2次?
when I used the charge card?
说, 艾德, 我爸妈到底
什么时候从欧洲回来?
Say, Ed, when do my parents
get back from Europe, anyway?
这个嘛, 很快了.
WeII, pretty soon.
有一个属于我们自己
的地方就好了.
It's neat having the pIace
aII to ourseIves.
先假装这里是我们的家吧.
Pretend it's ours.
假扮我们已经结婚了.
Like we were married or something.
好, 我们可以啊. 纳丁--
WeII, we can do that. Nadine--
然后我们就可以
干那回事了.
And there's some other stuff
we can do too.
嗯, 干哪回事?
WeII, Iike what?
你知道的, 傻帽.
You know, siIIy.
你知道我在想什么吗?
You know what I was thinking?
今晚我们可以去
湖边公园,
Tonight maybe we couId go park
by the Iake,
搂着脖子亲吻.
and neck.
等等.
Wait a minute.
其实我们那儿都不用去.
We don't have to go anywhere.
我们为什么不留在这儿呢.
Why, we can just stay right here.
你还是那么能偷嘛,
乔西.
You've kept yourseIf in fine nick,
Josie.
蓝宝石耳环,
Sapphire earrings,
巴黎香水,
Parisian perfume,
开士米羊毛衫.
cashmere sweaters.
你快走吧.
PIease go.
单程票.
One-way ticket.
西雅图, 香港.
SeattIe, Hong Kong.
- 我还有一天的时间呢.
- 你已经赚到了,见好就收吧.
- I have one more day.
- Keep what you earn.
赶快收拾
你的行李.
See what you can fit
into your suitcases.
我们今晚就走.
We Ieave tonight.
我还没收到
我的保险金呢.
I haven't received
my insurance money.
本·荷恩也还没付我钱.
And Ben Horne hasn't paid me yet
either.
我等了这些钱5年了.
I waited for this for five years.
埃卡先生会让你
得到比这更多的.
Mr. Eckhardt wiII make it more
than worth your whiIe.
你不能逼我走.
You can't make me Ieave.
顺势者昌.
Be adaptabIe.
我们有协议在先的.
We had an arrangement.
杜鲁门警长对你真的很重要.
Sheriff Truman is important to you.
但你欺骗他.
You Iied to him.
把他当猴耍.
You made him into a fooI.
话虽如此
但他对你还是很重要的.
But he is important to you
nonetheIess.
要不今晚和我走.
要不我杀了他.
Leave with me tonight.
Or I'II kiII him.
他什么都不知道.
He doesn't know anything.
今晚的飞机.
机场见.
The pIane Ieaves at midnight.
Be there.
要不我就来找你和你的警长.
Or I'II come for you and your sheriff.
就这样定了.
That's the arrangement.
- 嗨.
- Hi.
我想应该向你道歉.
I think I owe you an apoIogy.
没事啦.
Not reaIIy.
我们在一起的时候,
知道吗, 只是聊天,
WeII, when we were together,
you know, just taIking,
我也能感觉到点什么. 只是很模糊.
I feIt something. I just wasn't sure.
我让你想起了劳拉.
You Iooked at me and you saw Laura.
我想是吧.
I guess I did.
想知道
我的感觉吗?
Wanna know something
kind of strange?
什么?
What?
我喜欢.
I Iiked it.
真的?
You did?
我们从小一起长大,
When we were growing up,
劳拉和我是那么的亲近.
说出来怪吓人的.
Laura and I were so cIose.
It was scary.
我甚至能感觉到她在想什么,
I couId feeI her thoughts,
就像我们的脑袋
连在一起了.
Iike our brains were connected
or something.
她突然的死,
And when she died suddenIy,
给了我一个成为劳拉的机会.
I got the chance to be Laura.
而且大家也的确把我当作她了.
At Ieast other peopIe saw me that way.
就像你看我一样.
Like the way that you Iooked at me.
我也喜欢.
I Iiked that too.
但这是错的.
But it was wrong.
事情并不是非黑即白的.
It wasn't one thing or the other.
有时,
人就是需要扮演一下别的角色.
For a whiIe,
I got to be somebody different.
但现在我又是我了.
But now I'm just me again.
詹姆斯,
James,
你和唐娜彼此拥有着.
you and Donna beIong together.
真是太棒了.
That's the best thing.
- 有时也很辛苦, 你明白吗?
- 怎么说?
- It's just hard sometimes, you know?
- How?
如果真正去爱一个人,
If you reaIIy Iove someone,
就像是一盏大光灯
在永远照耀着你.
it's Iike this bright Iight
is shining on you aII the time.
在光环下的确很棒.
You're right in it and it's great.
但你不可能永远
在哪里呆着.
But I just don't think you can be
that way aII the time.
你当然可以.
Sure you can.
嗯, 希望吧.
WeII, I want to.
希望我的心
能永远跳下去.
I want to try to make the way
my heart feeIs Iast forever.
很怪异吧.
Pretty weird.
我打算明天回家了, 詹姆斯.
I'm going home tomorrow, James.
我来到双峰镇
参加劳拉的葬礼.
I came to Twin Peaks
for Laura's funeraI.
现在也该走了.
But now it's time to go.
这算道别了?
So is this goodbye?
算是吧.
I guess it is.
再见, 詹姆斯.
Bye, James.
火烧成功.
To the fire.
现在, 我真高兴得
不知说什么好了?
Now, to what do I owe
the pIeasure of this caII?
我已经拿到
有皮特签名的合约了.
I've got the contract
with Pete's signature.
我要我的那份钱.
And I want my money.
那还用说吗.
Of course you do.
全部. 马上.
在你拿到这个之前.
AII of it. Now.
Before you get this.
乔西, 乔西.
Josie, Josie.
你我的脑袋
都转的比水银还快
SureIy a mind
as quicksiIver as your own
能及时领会我们身处
的复杂情形.
can grasp the compIicated position
that we're in.
所以你知道, 灵活应变最重要.
FIuidity is everything, you know.
现在, 我手上
没有那么多的现金储备.
I can't summon up cash reserves
that I don't have.
但我会准备好的
But I have aIready
我很高兴的
再一次向你担保
and I wiII be happy
to assure you again
冰岛那边
的承包款
that as soon as
the contracted payments
很快就汇到了,
arrive from IceIand,
你的那份立刻
就成囊中物了.
your percentage wiII immediateIy be
passed on.
拿不到钱
我是不会走的.
I won't Ieave this office
without my money.
难道一点商量
的余地都没有吗?
Why do I sense
that this isn't a negotiabIe position?
你有压力,
对吧?
You're under some kind of pressure,
aren't you?
别再和我耍把戏了.
Do not pIay games with me.
把戏?
Games?
乔西,
Josie,
这是我酒店里
私人保险箱的钥匙.
this key unIocks
my personaI hoteI safe.
现在, 保险箱里,
Now, in that safe,
正放着你那份
魅力无穷的档案资料呢, 我亲爱的,
I have put together
a fascinating dossier on you, my dear,
你的死鬼丈夫--
安德鲁的那条小游艇会隆隆作响哦.
and your Iate husband--
Andrew's IittIe boat that went boom.
女士, 建议你别那么放肆,
So you behave yourseIf, Iady,
相信我能断送你的
大好前程.
or beIieve me when I say
that I wiII bury you.
那太可惜了.
That's a shame.
这一切如果真
不幸发生在我身上,
Because if anything unfortunate
were to happen to me,
那这个就会带警方
it wouId Iead authorities
追查到另一个城市银行里的
某个保险柜,
to a certain safety deposit box
in a bank in another city,
里面的证据
多得足以
inside of which
there is enough evidence
把你关3辈子.
to Iock you away for three Iifetimes.
他们会把我们肩并肩地埋在一起.
They wiII bury us side by side.
平局.
StaIemate.
你准备吧.
Your move.
现金.
Cash.
适时啊, 我正好能给你.
HappiIy, I can accommodate you.
刚签的约.
Sign of good faith.
东京银行.
Tokyo bank.
5百万美金.
Five miIIion doIIars.
我们两清了.
We are finished.
乔西.
Josie.
玩的不赖啊.
WeII pIayed.
敬里欧.
- Leo.
我们考虑到
你搞成了今天这个地步.
We sort of figured
with you getting out and aII.
好, 活见鬼了, 我们也该
给你来个小舞会庆祝.
WeII, what the heII, we sort of wanted
to give you a IittIe party.
用我们的话说,
"嘿, 里欧·强生, 欢迎回家."
Our way of saying,
''Hey, Leo Johnson, weIcome home.''
欢迎回家, 亲爱的.
WeIcome home, darIing.
因为你是特别嘉宾, 里欧.
我们只是想告诉你
Because you're a speciaI guy, Leo.
And we just want you to know
我们都记得你对你爱的人
都做过些什么好事.
that we remember aII the great stuff
you did for the ones you Ioved.
像雪莉.
Like SheIIy here.
一个温柔细心
又体贴的丈夫?
Who couId ask for a more caring
and thoughtfuI husband?
怎么能让她洗你的脏衣服.
为你洗盘子.
Making her cIean your dirty cIothes.
Wash your dishes.
擦地板.
你走狗运了, 呆子.
Mop your fIoors.
You're a cIass act, man.
- 生在福中不知福.
- 不知福.
- Top to bottom.
- CIass act.
And how about Leo Johnson,
虐妻狂?
wife abuser?
真值得为你开舞会庆祝了.
There's a guy I wanna party with.
把香皂套在丝袜里.
Soap in a sock.
把人打成内伤
却不留痕迹.
InternaI injuries
and bareIy Ieaves a bruise.
最后呢, 我想,
And Iast, but I'm thinking,
没有最后了,
not Ieast,
你里欧·强生栽在我们手上了, 谋杀罪.
we got Leo Johnson, murderer.
把自己的妻子
像肉一样吊起来.
Hanging your wife up
Iike a piece of meat.
让她吊在那儿炙烤.
Leaving her to burn.
难道就从来没人教过你
Don't Iet anybody ever teII you
怎么去善待
一位女士吗, 伙计.
you don't know how to treat
a woman, buddy.
这可是你的人生啊, 里欧·强生.
This is your Iife, Leo Johnson.
你下半生的煎熬.
You deserve it.
够你受的.
Every damn minute.
他动了.
He moved.
- 这太恐怖了. 我不要.
- 好了. 好了, 雪--
- This is too creepy. I don't Iike this.
- Okay. Okay, SheI--
好了, 可能你是对的.
Okay, maybe you're right.
我是说, 我是不应该利用他
去干些什么的.
I mean, I don't want to expIoit him
or nothing.
对不起, 里欧.
我们玩的有点过头了.
Sorry, Leo.
We sort of got carried away.
没有必要
把事情弄得更糟了.
No need to make your rehabiIitation
any more difficuIt than it aIready is.
海沃德医生说
需要对你进行一些刺激.
Doc Hayward said
you needed famiIiar stimuIus.
所以我们就想,
什么都好...
So we just figured,
what the heII...
...比如让你吹吹笛子.
...kazoos.
真的, 里欧.
Honest, Leo.
雪莉和我正
竭尽所能
SheIIy and me are going
to do everything we can
让你快乐安宁.
to make you feeI safe and happy.
嘿, 蛋糕怎样. 想来点蛋糕吗?
Hey, cake. You want some cake?
哦, 你看看.
Oh, Iook at that.
雪糕.
Ice cream.
波比.
Bobby.
嘿, 里欧. 哦, 哎呀.
Hey, Leo. Oh, jeez.
哥们儿, 你可得当心点.
Man, you gotta be more carefuI.
幸好我们还没点蜡烛呢.
Good thing we didn't Iight the candIes.
戴尔·库珀探员.
Agent DaIe Cooper.
戈登, 希望我没有
让你久等.
Gordon, I hope you haven't been
waiting too Iong.
何止久等. 我已经
等了你一下午啦.
I didn't just get here. I've been waiting
the whoIe afternoon to see you.
那我要怎么补偿呢?
What can I do for you?
免了.
也没必要歉疚.
No matter whatsoever.
No apoIogy necessary.
正好有时间让我
认识了这里的执法队.
Gave me a chance to meet
the IocaI Iaw enforcement team.
很棒的团队.
A great bunch.
库珀.
Cooper.
你一只微笑的吉娃娃狗
今天提醒了我.
You remind me today
of a smaII Mexican Chihuahua.
能和你
单独谈谈?
Can I speak to you
a moment in private, Coop?
好的, 戈登.
Of course, Gordon.
哈里, 能借用一下你的办公室?
Harry, can we use your office?
你或许问一下警长
我们是否能借用他的办公室.
You might ask the sheriff
if we couId use his office.
自便吧.
Go right ahead.
跟我来, 戈登.
FoIIow me, Gordon.
要保密, 库.
I beIieve in secrecy, Coop.
我很快说完. 但我不想
在他们面前说.
I'II make this fast. I didn't want
to say anything in front of the men.
艾伯特说你
被搞昏头了.
It's AIbert's opinion that you might be
getting in over your head.
这让我很担心, 库.
我觉得我也有责任.
This worries me, Coop.
I feeI a certain responsibiIity.
- 艾伯特错了, 戈登.
- 你还曾经在匹兹堡掉进瀑布呢.
- AIbert is wrong, Gordon.
- You went into the chute in Pittsburgh.
我必须要双保险,
甚至三保险,
And I want to make doubIy sure,
in fact tripIy sure,
这种事不会再发生了. 懂了?
that it does not happen again. Copy?
匹兹堡是另一件事了.
Pittsburgh was a compIeteIy
different story.
虽然我在匹兹堡也受伤过, 戈登,
I was wounded in Pittsburgh, Gordon,
但除此之外,
这2件案子再也没其他共通点了.
but beyond that,
the case bears no simiIarities.
你看起来还好.
I must say you Iook aII right.
只是有黑眼圈,
要注意睡眠.
Trace of circIes under the eyes,
catch up on your sIeep.
但多梦和不安
也会影响睡眠质量了.
But restIess nights and uneasy dreams
go with the territory.
我的确很累了, 戈登.
还有很多工作要完成.
I am tired, Gordon.
There is much work to be done.
但心, 身和魂
都上了发条了.
But mind, body and spirit
are up to the task.
毋庸置疑, 我顶得住.
Without a doubt, I'm A-okay.
你是我的骄傲, 库.
Proud of you, Coop.
好了, 戈登.
Now, Gordon.
墨西哥吉娃娃
到底是怎么回事?
What the heII is this
about a Mexican Chihuahua?
一个不寻常
麻烦事儿来了.
You've got a probIem
of a different sort here.
2加2不总是等于4的.
Two and two do not aIways equaI four.
我想应该告诉你, 你们在这里说的
我们在大厅都能听见.
You ought to know, we can hear
everything you're saying out in the haII.
- 进来吧.
- 为什么不请警长进来呢?
- Come on in.
- Why don't you invite the sheriff on in.
一封匿名信
寄去了总部
An anonymous Ietter sent
to home base
是寄给你的.
with your name on it.
很眼熟, 是吧?
Looks kind of famiIiar, doesn't it?
一个棋局.
It's a chess deaI.
好像是个棋局.
Looks Iike a chess deaI.
伟顿·厄尔
设的局.
It's an opening move
from Windom EarIe.
伟顿·厄尔.
Windom EarIe.
神祐你心, 库.
BIess your heart, Coop.
从现在开始
我们都得小心点了.
We're gonna have to watch
your back from now on.
因为杰利又不在, 嗯...
With Jerry on the road, weII...
我需要你回来帮我.
I need you back here.
可以说
Let's just say
你过去
几周的经历
that I have a much better sense
of what you've been through
- 我真是感同身受啊.
- 那太感激了, 本.
- in the Iast few weeks.
- I appreciate that, Ben.
感激你对我的信任.
真诚的.
And I appreciate the confidence.
ReaIIy I do.
如果不是那个起诉,
我本来想让你恢复原职的.
If it weren't for your indictment,
I couId drop you into your oId sIot.
你知道, 怎么多年朋友了,
同舟共济.
You know, our friendship,
our history together.
但首先, 我要知道
你能行吗.
But first, I need to know
that you're okay.
百分百, 本, 百分之1百10.
I'm 1 00 percent, Ben, 1 1 0 percent.
我会证明给你看的.
Let me prove it to you.
我们已经收到冰岛人
对『格斯伍』项目的投资款了,
We've taken a payment
from the IceIanders on Ghostwood,
但突然杀出队东方人
也极想参与这个项目.
but there's a group from the Orient
that wants in, in the worst way.
杰利已经去东京的路上了
去摸摸底,
Jerry is on his way to Tokyo
to check them out,
说不定已经到了
在看艺妓呢.
and probabIy every geisha
within a hundred miIes.
我会约这个大人物一起晚餐的.
I'm about to take Mr. Big to dinner.
但还需要一点时间.
We need to buy a IittIe time here.
好, 因为火灾
我们首先要把那块地重新测量.
WeII, the first thing we do
is resurvey the Iand.
还必须再重修一下.
Required because of the fire.
然后我们要建立起整一个
监察网络, 联邦, 县, 还有州,
Then we set up a whoIe parade
of inspectors, federaI, county, state,
直到杰利有完整的考察报告.
untiI Jerry gets back with a fuII report.
任何钱,
可以通过开曼群岛进出.
If there's any money,
we can run it thru the Caymans.
通过汇率
赚钱.
Pick up some money
on the exchange rate.
如有必要, 我们还可以把契约
放进黑洞六个月.
And if we have to, we can drop escrow
into a bIack hoIe for six months.
好样的，利兰.
That's my LeIand.
乔西?
Josie?
哈里, 你肯定
还没见过我的助手吧, 李先生.
Harry, I don't beIieve
you have met my assistant, Mr. Lee.
很高兴见到你.
PIeased to meet you.
我先把这些放上车.
I'II take these to car.
- 你在干嘛?
- 准备走啊.
- What are you doing?
- I'm going away.
去哪里? 为什么?
Where? Why?
哈里.
Harry.
乔西.
Josie.
我总是在这里给你电话.
I aIways caIIed you from here.
然后,
And then,
在这里，我能和你说说话...
it was here I couId taIk to you...
...做任何你想我做
的事.
...and be everything you wanted me
to be.
那, 留在这里.
WeII, then stay here.
我把锯木厂卖了. 一切都完了.
我只能回家.
I soId the miII. It's over.
I'm going home.
不.
No.
对不起, 别挂念我.
I'm sorry, don't think badIy of me.
李先生, 让我们单独呆会儿.
Mr. Lee, Ieave us aIone.
乔西, 你不能走.
Josie, you can't Ieave.
你要向警察举报我吗?
You saying this as the poIice?
不是.
No.
你最好还是忘了我吧.
It's best if you forget about me.
我爱你.
I Iove you.
乔西, 我爱你.
Josie, I Iove you.
- 要来点喝的么, 托吉麻辣先生?
- 不了, 谢谢你.
- WouId you Iike a drink, Mr. Tojamura?
- No, thank you.
你已经收了我
5百万美金的支票.
You have my cashier's check
for 5 miIIion.
而我什么还没收到.
I have nothing.
怎么回事?
Why?
这个嘛...
WeII...
其实我对你所知甚少,
托吉麻辣先生.
I know so IittIe about you,
Mr. Tojamura.
这是个很小的社区.
This is a smaII community.
万事都要小心.
I'm being carefuI.
尽量不要引起
太多关注.
Trying to be sensitive
to IocaI concerns.
希望你能理解舆论的影响和冲击
You must understand the impact
因为这个项目
将会在社区里进行的.
this project wiII have
on the community.
你在浪费我的时间.
You waste my time.
我们应该撤回资金.
We shaII withdraw.
啊, 别. 请别, 托吉麻辣先生.
Oh, no. PIease, Mr. Tojamura.
考虑一下我的立场和处境.
Consider the position that I'm in.
锯木厂的火灾造成了
一大堆无法预料的问题,
The miII fire created
a raft of unforeseen probIems,
心理上的以及财务上的.
psychic as weII as financiaI.
作为市长，我有责任和义务
I feeI it's my duty as a civic Ieader
帮助灾后重建和安慰市民.
to heIp foster the heaIing process.
也是我将来
Even at the temporary expense
长远发展的一个资本.
of my Iarger business opportunities.
我对火灾所知甚少.
I know a IittIe about fire.
我家在长崎.
My famiIy was at Nagasaki.
很抱歉.
I'm sorry.
慢慢认识你
Getting to know you
慢慢了解你的一切
Getting to know all about you
渐渐喜欢上你
Getting to like you
也希望你慢慢喜欢上我
Getting to hope you like me
慢慢认识你
Getting to know you
原谅我失陪一会儿?
WouId you excuse me a moment?
--但真好啊
--but nicely
你正是我所爱
You are precisely my cup of tea
你是哪里人, 先生?
Where might you foIks be from, sir?
- 就是双峰镇的.
- 那太棒了.
- Right here in Twin Peaks.
- That's terrific.
觉得那些修塔工怎样, 嗯?
How about those SteepIejacks, huh?
慢慢认识你
Getting to know you
渐渐感觉到自由和从容
Getting to feel free and easy
每当我接近你
When l am near you
渐渐懂得表达
Getting to know what to say
难道你还没察觉
忽然间,我变得活泼又聪明?
Haven't you noticed
Suddenly l'm bright and breezy?
因为一切都如此
美丽而新鲜
Because of all the beautiful
And new things
日复一日
l am learning about you
我学着读懂你
Day by day
谢谢你们, 女士们先生们.
谢谢你们.
Thank you, Iadies and gentIemen.
Thank you.
北方大酒店的观众
是全世界最棒的.
Great Northern audiences
are the greatest in the worId.
谢谢你们. 晚安.
Thank you. Good night.
- 大家路上小心.
- 国王与我.
- Drive carefuIIy.
- The King and l.
来休息一下, 利兰.
Give it a rest, LeIand.
间歇性神经错乱, 嗯?
Temporary insanity, huh?
正希望这些人
做你的陪审团.
HopefuIIy some of these peopIe
wiII be on your jury.
肯定判你无罪释放.
You wiII be home free.
你喜欢音乐剧吗?
You Iike musicaIs?
不喜欢.
No.
连『屋顶上的小提琴手』也不喜欢?
Not even Fiddler on the Roof?
它让我感动的哭得像个小孩.
It made me weep Iike a IittIe baby.
我认为对白日梦的所谓执着
都是徒添烦恼和不切实际的.
I find the adherence to fantasy
troubIing and unreasonabIe.
也许吧.
Yeah.
你不是这里人, 是吧?
You're not from around here, are you?
我是来旅游的.
I am a visitor.
哦. 这样, 那我请你喝清酒，好吗?
Yeah. WeII, couId I buy you a sake?
不, 谢谢了.
No, thank you.
或者来杯冻牛奶怎样?
Or how about a nice coId miIk?
请给我用药吧.
PIease give me my medicine.
- 我感觉到变化了.
- 什么变化?
- I can feeI the change.
- What change?
药是在他的东西里找到的
The drug found in his possession
药里含有一种
特强镇静成分.
contains trace eIements
usuaIIy found in HaIoperidoI.
你有精神分裂症?
Do you suffer from schizophrenia?
- 多重人格?
- 已经太迟了.
- MuItipIe personaIities?
- It's too Iate.
你认识这个人, 对吧?
上次我问你时为什么要撒谎?
You know this man, don't you?
Why'd you Iie when I questioned you?
- 那不是我. 难道你还不明白吗?
- 给他用药吧, 头儿.
- It wasn't me. Don't you understand?
- Give him the drug, chief.
- 还不能用.
- 如果我们给他用了药, 库,
- Not yet.
- If we give him the drug, Coop,
你就永远见不到他的另一面了.
you'II never see the other side.
- 快给他用药.
- 不.
- Give him the medicine.
- No.
根本不需要用药.
我一点儿也不痛苦.
There is no need for medicine.
I am not in pain.
你是谁?
Who are you?
- 我是迈克.
- 你是什么?
- My name is Mike.
- What are you?
我是栖息在这个体内的另一个灵魂.
I am an inhabiting spirit.
那菲利普·杰勒德又是谁?
Who is PhiIIip Gerard?
他是我的主人.
He is host to me.
你在我的梦里
You spoke to me in my dream
提到鲍勃.
about Bob.
他是我的常客了.
He was my famiIiar.
鲍勃从哪里来的?
Where does Bob come from?
那是不能透露的.
That cannot be reveaIed.
那鲍勃想要什么?
What does Bob want?
这个鲍勃, 很贪玩.
He is Bob, eager for fun.
他面带微笑,
He wears a smiIe,
人人都跑了.
everybody run.
你知道寄生虫吗?
Do you understand the parasite?
它以依附作为生命形式
和进行自我喂养.
It attaches itseIf
to a Iife form and feeds.
鲍勃则需要人类做寄主.
Bob requires a human host.
以吸食人类的恐惧
He feeds on fear
和快感为生.
and the pIeasures.
他们都是他的孩子.
They are his chiIdren.
我和鲍勃是同类人.
I am simiIar to Bob.
我们曾经是好伙伴.
We once were partners.
- 在黑暗中穿越未来过去
- Through the darkness of future past
- 魔术师渴望找到
- The magician longs to see
一个机会连接2个世界之间的出入口
One chance out between two worlds
与火同行
Fire walk with me
但是后来我看到了上帝的脸
But then I saw the face of God
是多么的纯净.
and was purified.
于是我把手砍了下来.
I took off the arm.
但剩下的还在飞船附近.
But remained cIose to this vesseI.
有时栖息
只为了一个单纯的目的.
Inhabiting from time to time
for one singIe purpose.
- 找到鲍勃.
- 并制止他.
- To find Bob.
- To stop him.
这就是他的原样.
This is his true face.
但极少人能看见.
But few can see it.
除了那些有天赋的...
The gifted...
...和被诅咒的人.
...and the damned.
现在鲍勃在我们附近?
Is Bob near us now?
在这儿游荡将近40年了.
For nearIy 40 years.
在哪儿?
Where?
一间大木屋.
A Iarge house made of wood.
被树木围绕着.
Surrounded by trees.
屋子里有很多房间,
每间都一模一样.
The house is fiIIed with many rooms,
each aIike.
但住着不同的灵魂.
But occupied by different souIs.
夜夜如是.
Night after night.
北方大酒店.
The Great Northern HoteI.